Welcome to the madness
It's 9 p.m. Lights up Mike's hot chaos in the stream Vita calling in slurring words starting up a scene talking all that trash
Then she flips rage queen mad at me girl, please the show runs on caffeine
Sides twisted laughing loud whiskey in his veins slurs flying left and right we cut the feed no shame
But the chat's on fire can't tame this flame. This ain't your mama
podcast this a runaway train welcome to the madness buckle up tight boob flashing on cam chat
losing air mines michael getting gong alex taking flight it's wild it's wrong and we do it every
night page got him simping hearts in the chat but she ain't got time for a dude like that diamond
flirting hard let the girls react it's a freak show party no filter all fat
Yo Michael drops a line gong not tonight Alex tried to joke boom sent into the night
Panel looking sideways. Someone's got a fight producers on mute praying this don't spike diamonds feeling spicy shirts slipping down low
Oops, she says with a wink
We're trending in the press
The vibe
What's up psyche? What's up? What's up? That kind of looks like you in that video a little bit too. I think so. I know. She was with some hotties in that video. Yeah. Pretty amazing. It's so realistic. I wish I looked like that guy, but. Yeah, the ghost takes all the way to the ghost.
Yeah, I want to get my haircut actually doubt nothing. I will
Last time I got my haircut, I put in a picture of Ryan Gosling. I think he was like
There we go, hey ghost
Did you like uh
Go what's your name is that video too? Did you hear your name?
Let's go. I don't know. I can't hear him very well.
Go ahead, go ahead, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk guys, talk
I love you. I love you. I
appreciate you guys. It's just
we have the last hour. Let's
make it fun. We have one hour
left. Let's uh have a fun
night. Well, if I paid for it,
can I own the last hour?
Uh, yeah, I'll I'll I'll take off. Yeah, it's already pretty you can't you gotta pay
Off too bad paid for you don't fuck. I know you don't know
You don't it means
Man
Okay, bye-bye
Again oh
And this is what I've been looking for all day. I did this.
How much money did you give Summer?
I just picked up the newspaper of the cop box put in jail. How much money did you give? You heard my question. How much money did you give?
Tonight? Nothing. You're giving all the money. I don't have to pay. Any night, but other nights, other nights.
I get money. So don't worry about my money. I get okay. You get money by how much good enough?
Yeah, enough enough to make my seat
Summer here
You're gonna have to pay again. You're gonna have to pay again. I already paid
I'm fucking already pay again motherfucker. Come on. Hey, baby. I did
need a bitch. You are. I'm going to go. You said five minutes. You did say five
minutes. You don't get to take on it. I'm a friend. I'm a friend. It's done an
overweight. Uh, she lost it. I paid a lot of money. No.
Well, you should have you should have talked about that when you paid it
I've already did my two five minutes now. You got to deal with me. You don't like it pay again, bitch
Nobody paid for five minutes
Yes, you did. Yes, you did you said all I want is five minutes for her
Fucking thing was
Hey
Yes, and I should have my panel right well too bad
That's not the way this works. You get a panel
You picked it already
I'm gonna be right here. I'm gonna be right here to bug you
Yeah, I paid 70 don't fuck I can hear your husband talking I
This is my son
And my son's not gonna argue with a fucking idiot. I raised a man on a bitch. I'm not trying to argue
I just have more money. All right, then check the fuck up
But I have more money than like I said now and you don't have more money in my son. I can promise you that I do
I do now. You don't know you don't
I just I just
And you spend money on a fucking panel, that's a
No fucking money already paid done fuck
Yeah, you guys are so security check and spend all of it. I mean, that's not my fucking problem. Come on bro. Come on, bro
I sponsor panel of it when he's I've ever gone. I need to actually save me just for you to have money
Pay me bitch. Well, actually don't pay me pay pay psyche
All right, let's go. It has a crush on this summer. Yeah
I look for that fucking newspaper all day and it was like you come on dude
Yeah, I want to see something there. You want to see something? This is what I did
Have you ever done that? Have you ever put a cop in prison?
Did that
Did he leave?
Is he up here or am I up here by myself?
I win!
Howler!
Because I will give you at least, you know, I'll give you some more time for panels,
but at least one of them will be your choice of who to have on,
so I'll give you that choice, okay?
Because you're gonna donate about 100 bucks tonight, so you know.
You did better off, it better not be a night that I'm here, motherfucker.
Howler!
You want to play games, but you ain't fucking got big enough balls to play with me, bitch. I can promise you that
And you can even school my fucking son cuz I'll run circles around your goofy ass, too
Well, I don't know where he went with you in the chat now. Let me see. No, he's going. Okay, goes, you know, but we'll do it again goes, you know, you'll you'll get another one. Well, we'll cry, cry me a fuck a river like Justin just a beaver with a kid's name and sing itself. Yeah.
Yeah
No matter how much yeah, Justin's ever like there you go. No matter how much money you got you ain't got bigger balls than me
You ain't never gonna be able to outlast this mouth
Where's everybody else at anybody in the back, I don't know I did in the link and so everyone's welcome up
You know, I've been using like I uh, you know, I upgraded the chat GPT because it's basically like having like a
Full-time like expert employees
Okay, okay summer
Did you pay another chat? Yeah
Five minutes before you kick me off in the back it's five minutes because he didn't pay the full 25, right?
Okay, well it goes. What are you thinking for the right? I mean, it's like I don't think it's gonna be longer than
He just came get enough of the summer lovin
Ghost made a ghost made it rain tonight. It's made it rain. Okay. He did make it rain. That's okay
I don't mind going to the back. He needs specific how much time I'm going in the back though. So I know
Okay, okay
Can you please answer that um ghost? Thank you. I'd love to thank you
I don't mind going in the back, but you can tell me how long that way. I know whether I should start a panel or not
Okay, yeah, just let her know goes
Summer's a good sport
Hey, RG. Hey, everybody and yeah
Be mad, but it's like no, but I'm gonna make you act like a trick in a strip club. You don't spend your money today, baby
Fucking idiot
Hey
Give a fuck about his lame ass money, bitch
Dear fucking entertainment, that's all this is
Stockings, bitch, I'm talking to you, psychies pack, it's getting fat
I
And I'm still on panel talking shit, bitch.
I'll work.
Yo, Kiyos, you have to say it.
You have to say it.
Specify it.
You have to specify it.
You have to say something in the...
How long have I gone for?
You haven't paid $75 and you still ain't told us how long I'm gone for.
You fucking idiot.
He's such a fucking, you can spend all the money in your world you want, but bitch you
can't buy character motherfucker.
But go specify, go specify, how long, you can say it, just say how long okay?
Yeah, come on pussy, how long, how long you gonna bear me for bitch?
Yeah
She's not answering goes so it's helping exactly not forever. Okay, I think you know, it's like
A lot more money than a couple hundred bucks to get rid of me forever bitch. I'm content motherfucker. I ain't going nowhere
Go so you come back up then
Then I'll you know, but you get to say like exactly like the
I love you. I love you. I love
you. I love you. I love you.
I love you. I love you. I love you.
That's gonna make a hundred percent sure it's the right person.
Oh, where'd she go? I want I want to talk to her.
Um, she's, oh, at least she might be still here. Hold on. Hold on.
Yeah, she's still here. Summer. I'm still here, motherfucker.
Hi, Summer. Hi, girls.
You know what I would rather not I paid all that money to I'd rather not have you kicked off
Because I do like to talk to you and if you if you want to talk I'm down for it
I'm still going to talk to you mother fucker. I'm still going to talk to you. I'm going to talk to you tonight. I'm going to talk to you tonight. I'm going to talk to you tonight. I'm going to talk to you tonight. I'm going to talk to you tonight. I'm going to talk to you tonight. I'm going to talk to you tonight. I'm going to talk to you tonight. I'm going to talk to you tonight. I'm going to talk to you tonight. I'm going to talk to you tonight. I'm going to talk to you tonight. I'm going to talk to you tonight. I'm going to talk to you tonight. I'm going to talk to you tonight. I'm going to talk to you tonight. I'm going to talk to you tonight. I'm going to talk to you tonight. I'm going to talk to you tonight. I'm going to talk to you tonight. I'm going to talk to you tonight. I'm going to talk to you tonight. I'm going to
when you roasted me the other night you talk back shit to me all fucking night the other night so you
can go fuck yourself you can kick me out panel if you want that's fine all I'll do is tomorrow when
I come back I'm gonna make you spend more money because I'm gonna be on that motherfucking asshole
goddamn night so you make the fucking decision well can I ask open the fucking door make that
fucking decision I'll open the panel up open the panel up are you gonna be okay you're crashing
Who am I? I'm nobody stop catching on to me.
Spent 25. Are you going to be on me, Cole?
Get me kicked. I'm going to be each summer. I'm going to be me.
I'm going to keep doing what I'm doing right now so either I'm banned or I'm not.
Are you going to be fair Summer?
I'm always fair. I'm going to be in the ass.
I'm going to be because this man who hired me the other night when you called me a whore and everything else.
So go fuck yourself bitch. All right. That sounds fair.
Oh, that sounds fair. I'll let you you're here
You can't change your mind in five minutes just so you know
But it's be cool. Why are you crashing out?
I'm just giving you the same energy you gave me and spunky the other night and page when you called all of us fucking horse
Well, they do sound like whores. I mean, what's the argument?
Yeah, you tried it. You tried it next time
Put more money up she's been would you like to be next sir if you got twenty five dollars been yeah
You're going to anybody else put another twenty five dollars. You're gonna have to pay. Let's run that bitch dog
I dare you. No, you're you both are gone. Oh, we're both gone. So you can be talking
Anybody else want to talk drop drop listen drop 50 and you ban me and summer together. Hey, but you got a specified
Okay
Fuck off
No, you're not. You're like here. You're a fuck.
And thank you to sit here and play your way through the fuck alive. Go fuck yourself. Hey, you know if you've been me and somebody
You got nobody to talk to right you do know
All right, do this anybody else
You say by my fuck we ain't say bye
Well, I paid for you guys
You did
Did you tell psyche here? There's this $25
Yes
Where's the money at I
Don't know check the chat you fucking record psyche get him out of here
psyche get him out of here
I
Where did it say bad summer or bad turn?
Where did it say that I
Think so I think so full back small back
So you having fun now, you didn't chase everybody away. We was all laughing. We thought having a good time
Yeah, sir. I didn't chat. I didn't say it's like the way to stay alone. I gave him money. I didn't chase him away, but I'm not
I'm just gonna meet up and let you talk to yourself, bitch. So let me and let me talk to psyche
Go fuck yourself. Can I not talk to you? I paid a lot of money to talk to you there. That's true
Truth are you there?
That you should so yes me. What's up? Okay. Let's make you sure. Okay. One second. There you go
What up, so?
What's that man? What's good? I'm selling baby. How are you?
This is this is like
I feel like
I'm gonna get you right now. I'm gonna get you right. I'm gonna get you right. Yeah, I want
Okay, but okay, but because you said I told her she said 24 hours and she was
Done and then you said bring her back and then you said, okay
Oh, well, you should have made that
You should pay $70 to kill the panel man. You
He's a pussy
Yeah, I wonder gone never mind. I think
Picking shoes you can't do that
Yes, and he told it you hold on hold on hold on you pay you 70 dollars to have a kick up the pound
This ain't no matter how long I don't have $70 ever gone
So what's your not not true? No, no, what he did was he donated to the channel, right?
And then when he felt some type of way when he felt some type of way, then he said, oh, I want my money to go towards
Banning summer
It don't work like that. It does not work
Spin that paper man. Hey spin that paper
You spin another fiddle. I bet you won't do it. I bet you won't
Look, I've got twenty-five to get done right here.
It's just...
Ooh!
Ooh, hello.
Right up.
I don't have that much money.
Did that make you happy?
Did he make you mad?
Oh
A bunch of girls were up here showing their tits to each other. That's what pissed him off the other night
That just got me tingling and so if I
A lot of money so you'd have this argument brother get her going. I paid a lot of money. I'm in a good mood
I don't even want to fight shit
You can keep him though just get rid of her keep the guy
No, no, no, no, no, it's not that you don't know you got expensive you got to say psyche look
I'm sending you twenty five dollars being
Anybody
Goes fuck your fucking money goes real shit. Fuck you will fuck your money clown. You're a bozo
You know what the fuck you're talking about, sir
I do I know you're a bozo and I can't wait to see you everybody
Give me 10 seconds, I'll get you hey
Kick her out
Now I start with me because I'm beyond your bumper start with me
I'm gonna get you next white night
Spend 50 and say is for summer
So don't however you want and so
Hey
He's about to and change he spent some he spent like
I've record everything
He said well, you know what actually don't ban him for 24 hours just put her in the back for five minutes
So he paid two on some dollars to put me in the back for five minutes each time
You can cut my pen on paper man have everybody put in the back for that long if you gonna do that, bro
Let him on my panel
Now I'll put all the niggas in the bag. They can all get kicked off
And the argument started the other night like I said there were about three or four hot chicks up here
And we showed each other our boobs not any of the dudes we were showing each other
Fuck what you got recording in the back or
Bitch and spend some money
You are spending money
Trit am I am you gonna put her back or am I getting my money back?
I
Went back in the back for five minutes. You brought me back. You said you didn't want me gone for 24 hours
Yeah, it's really over and I'll see you tomorrow
I'll be here. I hope you bring your possible bitch
a ghost
Ghost I don't have everything a ghost. You've seen what I had last night, right?
I'm done talking to you. I'm
That's what I had last night right there
Or I don't
Yes, and he got offended when I posted adult
Check the score I
I'm just trying to take it to the court. Why are you trying to beat me up, sir? Why are you doing that?
Look what?
I'm just trying to take it to the court. Why are you being mean?
Well, you be
I don't blame you true
You're the pussy
On your mouth
Somebody wrote past me and said meow that's a hell
I don't see everybody grow mad hit me summer. I don't somebody record this summer stop hitting me
From right being so
You like what I beat you because that's why you paid I don't like it. I don't like it
Please stop hit me
Now
If this is dude on the picture right here as your avatars that's ghosts you look like Bobby from King of the hill
Needle like a fat blowfish you look like faster you like do from Adams family faster with her
I'm fucking like a gerber with with with a mustache funny face motherfucker. He pales a motherfucking slice of bread
Yo, don't he look like Chun-li from pool
Fat catfish roasting session
Yo, Chumlee don't
Just know that fuck yeah, fuck all of you. Let's run it
Run what goes?
I have defense.
I have all good.
You look like a baby.
You look like a baby rock robber with no teeth.
I guarantee I run good.
Come on, dumb dumb.
Do
Straight out of the trailer park straight out of motherfucking trailer park
Garbage
What do you mean sure the part garbage
Explain yourself the burden if it was on you the fuck you mean
You shut your bitch
How am I ghetto where am I you don't have to fuck you're talking about these on a psyches panel, bro
You're gonna be quiet aren't you you're gonna be quiet aren't you gonna sit there near shut the fuck up aren't you
We're gonna suck my dick
You ain't got nothing
Oh
Use that for next by a woman sexual for 200-something dollars
Also
I always win, you dumbass, I always win, you dumbass
You use that for next one with 300 hours of my sight, man
You're the next little bitch's ass
What you like when you use small words?
He got more money than you, you broke ass
All right, dumb dumb
No, you got for next one, you're a woman sexual
I'm still winning, I'm still winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I'm winning, I
They never wish
Don't you have, like, better money for wasted money on a PS5 or something like that?
You said
that before y'all just mad because I want you play a little bit of my
crap once you push on your keyboard you're never gonna run me you said you
always win but you just lost 200 on that bitch dog yeah I'm thinking I like to
throw hands
You always
Man still question smash. He say he always wins
I
but you fucking you had a grocery
to make in the morning you did this
now fuck the groceries I want this man
yeah star bitch
let's run it
you're not gonna run it are you
you're too much of a pussy
did you just say you want this man
I want some man
I want to run it let's run it
I'll live for this shit
you realize we're on line right
the
Yeah pussy
Let's run that bitch
Are you gonna say you're not making no sense?
No, you're spending all it is bread again. I'm making no
I don't understand that I don't understand I can make the argument any
Topic
Just scared to have it and it's up there and shut the fuck I'm gonna talk baby. Come on. Let's pick it. How about
Alright, that's a good one go ahead who said that
I said, well one of the two should should should want me to be allowed to vote or
Should second amendment be intact, you know, like it's that what's in that positive the second amendment, you know
I agree with you straight up
Listen, this is the man of the base yet. He's
He just likes drama that's all he likes you won't engage in no debate
So I'm waiting for the day
Topic I'm waiting for the day
Lice to stir people's emotions and argue with them
Fuck up welcome to sake you panel. Say your name, please. Yeah, I'm here Patrick
Who?
I'm here Patrick. It's seven
the
Yo, this dude's a broken wedgie!
He's a broken wedgie!
A good guy, man. He's spending the big bucks tonight.
Well, I'm not broke. I didn't see my girls tonight.
I didn't see my girls tonight.
You won't engage in any debate topics, ghost.
That's what I mean, man.
What time?
Listen to you for about six months, bro.
You won't engage in any debate topics.
That's why you like it here.
You like to get a bunch of people arguing.
You like to be the sinner.
to be fair there was a topic that was being displayed here the second about the second amendment
And stay I want to be fair stay turd was actually
Being engaged. Yeah, he was
We actually did say second
Ghost deraility because he didn't want to be a part of the actual debate
I want to be fair like stay turn was actually being good faith
You know, he didn't go to deraility because he wanted there to be any good discuss good discussion
Let me talk to stay
Why are you running your fucking mouth shut up?
That's be quiet
That's all you know is like slurs and cursing people out and like go actually have a conversation
He's very he can barely do that dude. Let me let me end of this one. Let me
Ask what you're thirsty for a debate, but you never bring up a topic. Never not what he's not thirsty for a debate
He's thirsty for the attention
But it's a yeah, but his favorite word is debate debate pick a time
Fucking I'll take one the fucking I'll take one before what's one matter so go ahead
the number one master debater
that's the only time you're going to think you're going to win
you ain't going to win though but I'll fucking dig it
not even not even master debater is master favorite
go ahead let's run it
run the clip
I choose not to think you're going to run that passion
studio chat
too stupid to have the conversation
I want the name of speakeasy
yeah that's another thing
he has like a checklist of things that he says
Let's run. Let's do it. I have a conversation is one retarded.
That's running.
That dumb dumb is another.
How many times have I told you?
What else do I have to say?
I'm gonna crash out as another.
I feel like I'm gonna crash out as another.
I never once said that.
I never once said that, by the way.
Please run it.
You're gonna say, you're gonna say, please.
You're gonna say crash out eventually.
if not, then shut the fuck up
because you don't want to fuck up
so let's re-engage that second amendment talk dude
go ahead guys, start it off
you don't know what the second amendment is?
sir, sir, sir
I'm asking you to educate me on what the second amendment is
I'm asking you sir, I'm asking you
since I don't know what it is, please educate me on what the second amendment is about
I don't know. It might be about guns. Do you know anything about that?
It might be about guns. Okay, okay. So how do you feel about guns?
It might be. How do you feel about guns?
How do you feel about guns?
Hold up matter of fact hold on general gentleman. I got one for him. Hey ghost. Let me ask you a question
You want to talk I got
Okay, so the second amendment states that every American should be
Have the rights of their arms, correct?
Yeah, don't fuck okay, so let me ask you a question if somebody commits a crime
Does some jail time it has a felony should that person lose their second amendment? Yes or no?
Are you allowed to own a gun if you commit a felony if you don't are you allowed to own a gun?
That's my question that that that's my question. Yes. That's my argument
Listen Richard. You got to answer the question though. If you're a phone are you allowed to own a gun?
He was
If anybody committed a felony today, the right to bear arms.
But sir, sir, sir, sir, sir, if you're a felon,
does your right to a felon, sir?
Psyche, if you're listening to Summers in the back.
Does your rights go away, dumb fuck?
He's not, he's not.
The right to bear arms, does it go away?
That's what I am asking you.
Sum you up, let's sum her up.
That's what I'm asking you, you dumb fuck.
No, dude, it was my argument you I'm asking you a question. It's a question
Do you feel like a felon should have their second
Listen you a
I listen I try to bring up a topic. You're just a fucking idiot.
I don't know why the Bay was to you.
Oh, shit. Thank you. I needed that.
Everyone calm down to bowing your hair.
I thought everybody was a ghost.
Chill out.
You know, I gotta switch my avatar for that
because I'm probably turning some of my off right now.
Alright, but no talking about stuff like that.
You're changing stuff from my dum-dum.
See I was able to take a deep breath. No, you're up early this morning. I
Just got
Gonna work you do
Give me a compliment. I just couldn't hear you man
That's that was me, dude
of the
house and goes left and spending a fortune of
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you're actually asking a good faith and trying to engage there and just like
No, that kind of pisses me off a little bit because girls came on another
Content creators channel paying money for help. I'm like, well fuck it. Let's run it. I come on here finding out
He's the one being the asshole. So because they turn actually was actually acting in good faith and I'm seeing it now
That's why I got on you summer because you were acting a little, you know, you're being obnoxious, but
But i found out who the real asshole was and i'm kind of
being pretty hella stupid. I'll admit it. I'll fucking admit it.
You're good. Welcome to the crazy house, baby.
We're having fun.
And so they see that it's all love right there. We don't hold grudges. You know what? Like if I
got a problem with somebody, it's my fault. I'll admit. You just did the same thing with her.
That's amazing. I love it. I love it.
That's how
Some fire-ass roast and shit, you know, but but you know, I like to use it what it was really needed
But you know, I meant I was being stupid because mother fucker made me feel stupid
You know, I don't like that like someone
Speak easy loves me let me tell you
Yeah
Loving words encouragement about you, but you know like my personal thing is that I want to go off of my experience
They go off what I go through not what someone else tells me about some certain things
Well, I appreciate that that's very rare on these streets. That's really awesome because that's very rare
I
Told you he'd be back
I want to be quiet well, you know watch this yeah, and we got cookies on too
Not just goes he look at me and I did face you want to know how this all started me and goes
They're actually cool, but the other night there was a couple six all over here and
We were all like, you know just like this go like this one and he fucking lost his shit
Hey, you fucking whores you fucking so every since then now I've told him horse
You did call me a whore. Yes, you did you call all of us whores you called me paid
Yes, you did yes, you did
That's why
Well, you did that night. You gave a fuck about me page
Funky, yeah
He dragged us for three hours calling us whores and demanding to talk to my husband and demanding to talk to us
I mean like it was it was crazy. I talked to your husband. No you didn't
I wish there was a man that he was a director of it.
They turned to me longer than you and my husband doesn't come on panel, sweetie.
Unless I'm on every now and then, he'll say, hey to everybody,
but other than that, he doesn't come on panel.
He doesn't do anything.
He'll make a cab.
That was my son just a minute ago.
He'll make a cab me on in summer's life.
Oh, man.
He popped in every now and then, said, what's up,
and then you see him in the background going about his business.
That's it.
Yep.
My husband always knows what I'm doing. He always knows every first one my husband my best friend and he just like he said
I told him I told him what happened and he was like babies like so what you and the girls were having a little bit of fun
Who cares?
My husband's not an insecure prick. He's not worried about a bubble on YouTube still in his wife
a fucking fake electronic person.
And we're all up here having a good time.
We're all having fun.
Me and Ghost has hung out with,
me and Ghost know each other for a while now
and Ghost has always had my back.
So when he did that the other night,
I was like, damn, dude, really?
Cause we're showing fucking, we're shaking some titties.
Like you act like we went and fucked your girl or something.
And yeah, how would you be,
how could you be mad at titties though?
Like you're, you're, you claim you're a straight man.
Summer I want to ask you who's that guy in the truck that was in the video of your shorts, right?
It's my husband and you keep asking me that and it's a old picture my husband's lost weight since then
Okay, so that's your husband you're that guy driving the truck when you were driving the Cincinnati
Yeah, okay
For 18 years. All right, then that's good. Congratulations
Thank you very much
Rarity I'm actually married to a really good guy. He puts up a watch it. So he's got to be decent
That's the important thing
true
He's able to borrow and contain
18 years
God damn
Honestly you don't look you don't look bad for for someone in their 40s and that's just a compliment. I'm not trying to raise you know
Well, thank you very much
Yeah
God man, I'm a few what few years away from 40 fuck then brother that that was a compliment
But you say for somebody in their 40s like 40 is old a song
It's not
When you turn for you realize if 40 is not old at all, and you'll be like damn
I was such an idiot telling people 40 was a hoed
But it's my 40s. Oh
Yo
Summer I'm gonna tell you something. I'm gonna tell you something. I don't move a fuck up. I say it on live
I'll say it on a stream everything right when I first turned 30
I got mad emotional. I damn near cried like oh shit. I'm turning 30. I'm going out of my 20s
What the fuck like I really like dirty hit me hard dirty hit me hard like
that I was happy that I'm actually like, I got a little bit of sympathy, not much, but a little bit, so, me and 40s didn't bother me, it doesn't bother me at all
I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you
of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of
No, not speak. Uh, no, you're talking to me. Yeah. How old are you man? I'm 39
But I'm about to hit 40 and like and like another month or two
I'm not gonna say exactly but another month or two. I'll be 40. Yeah, it's just a number
Yeah, I got five years. I don't worry about it. I thought you're closer. It's just easy and restraining us
some bodies restreaming because that's probably where the echoes coming from
I've muted myself
yeah I know I went
what's up speed easy how you going
some are gonna do her homework I know some about to do that homework
I don't care it's like you don't give a fuck of people who restrain them so I mean yeah
it doesn't matter
Yeah, I knew you was going to find out though. Oh
Speak easy listen if you're gonna like restream all good brother just join
Put your two cents and you are is he in the backstage there's a guy in the backstage there
What's his name?
Tiki's turf zone is in the back right choose on
the
How come you people are in bed now? It's 6 a.m. Here
Can't sleep, huh?
Insomnia
I'm in a night. I can't sleep. Oh
You're on a night schedule
that
the
I know that's good
Well before my all my inner work, you know, because my kids are older now and so they're all working on shit
But but before they all started working they would all go to we all we had a big family membership and everybody wants to the gym
nice
And my husband I'm really proud of him. He's been working his ass off. He's looking pretty shot these days
Hey, there you go. Some of you you saw you still go to the jump to the gym or not
Yeah, I just I went matter of fact. I went right before I went to work
I went and did a little 30 minute workout and then what's in them real quick because I was busy
The last two days, so I didn't get a chance. So I try to steal. I don't know if she's birthday. So I'm just you know
Tighten it up a little bit
Nice nice nice
Tighten up what I was checking out some of your video somewhere the other day when I had nothing to do
Yeah
And I left you a 40% discount for liposuction surgery. If ever you need it
All right
Thank you, though, that's okay a token a little token of my generosity there
cool
If you need it that is if you don't I don't need it. I like my body. I've had babies and everything and I'm great
I got a baby a two-year-old daughter my cat
Awesome. Oh, she's a beauty. I
Bet she's a cutie. Yes, she's awesome
Yo, you know how many kids summer popped out and still got that body
Do you know are you do you have any idea?
That's all gravy. I ain't worried about what he thinks. He's a bubble. I'm just curious. Like, do you know? Do you have any idea?
Take a guess. How many how many how many babies do you think summer popped out and still has that body?
Well crickets crickets, who are you talking about?
He's talking to you, I think
the
No, you better you know
Go
You got more than three. Okay. Yeah, take another get
Well, yeah, she's in shape man. He's in very good shape. Take another guess. I
Don't know man. I don't know you guess. I don't care. No, I know you take a guess. I
know five six
eight
Well, I burst seven all together, but so
Seven that's crazy
That still look like that and didn't let their body go that come on now that that deserves, you know
But hey, we'll take all the
He he dropped. Oh the Sebastian guy. Yeah. Yeah, they're all that said has a funny way of flirting. He's never talked to
Christine chose violence day, I better watch out
Yes, it's okay Justin you better be careful off fuck your girl holler
I'm just kidding
Love is I love your chick. She's awesome
Sam will you let said back in he accidentally hit the wrong button?
Hmm
I don't think I like I don't think I like that game
Nah, he's good. He's just he's just yeah, it's entertainment, dude
One thing I've learned over the last couple years is just especially when you're in a community like you just got to laugh and have fun
I've raged out on so many fucking people now. Just let's have a good time. Fuck it. They can say I'm fat
They can say I'm old they can say all whatever they want. I'm everything
My voice over the guy. I'm just saying in general, you know
Hey Justin, I definitely might have felt better than you. I promise you I could fuck your girl way better than you could
Either he now he didn't take you off panel. I got thick skin. It's like he knows that
I'll leave if I have an issue with somebody
I ain't unless I ban somebody for like, you know, I did the other night with ghosts when he was talking shit
The panel is ending as soon as they drop off wait. No. Why is everybody where are we ended?
I'll start a panel
Like you're tired if you're tired just let me know we can drop my talk your ish link and we can go over there
Oh
No, I didn't know where I didn't know what's going on. It's like I didn't know if he was tired or oh
Because if he's tired then I mean it is six in the morning, but I just got off work
So I don't mind open on a panel up if he wants to
I work third ship to so it's like sometimes it sucks to because my schedules off black because I work
Like let me give you an idea how my works get my my day-to-day schedules like I'll get off work sleep three hours
Wake up six sleep to go to work for eight go to sleep or four wake up for it's not say, you know
It's all over the place. I'm gonna
Like a nine to five or a set schedule where I can have some decent sleep and it sucks ass and
I have to pick up my wife in the middle of the day
Even like I get a good sleep, you know, like that good nice deep sleep. You're just knocked out you wake up because you got it sucks
No, I get it. I do so I do I clean offices and stuff at night
But then I do a lot of different community type of work
They're on the day and the rest of the time when I'm not sleeping and so yeah, I have my sleeps all over the fucking place
I get it a
Boy you you said you got my IP address
Once you put it out there family you said you got it
Put it out there or use it like let's hang out have a beer
Yeah, man, pull up we'll have a beer
Yeah, man
My IP address unless there's some type of fucking computer hacker
Sige wake the fuck up
Sikey porn bomber a pump on a whole lot pump on my psyche psyche
I'll try to get his attention
Hey, yo boy, oh
Well, I live at boy
Well, you guys can hit the link or you can hit the talk your ish thing and I think I might just go ahead and start a panel
the
some sleep
I'm not for like another five minutes
maybe
Well, I'm gonna drop down and charge my phone
We'll see how everything goes if he doesn't answer anything. I'll start it if people want me to I'll start a panel if not
Just fucking whatever
I do you think something you have a good one? All right, baby, too
All right, you guys have a good night. Excuse me. Oh, I'll be in the chapter now, too
Stay turn you have a good night. I'm hopping off as well
All right, peace man. Have a good one. I'm out to
Boy oh, where the fuck do I live boy you talk to me
Where's my IP address leading you to? Let me know stay turn wants to know
Stay turn wants to know where you found
The IP address and where it is located you have my full if you found it you have my full permission
To type it in a chat right now gang
It's not doxing I'm if you found it
I'm giving you my full permission to put it in the chat right now.
This is not considered doxing.
You got the skills?
Put it in the comments Pussy.
Stay turn sign off piece a oh boy
Tell spunky matter of fact don't tell spunky nothing just on give spunky a kiss for me. All right. Mm-hmm. That's for spunky, right?
But kisser on the other lips, I mean not the top lips on the bottom lips peace game
Welcome to the night, the cards laid out for show
Star shine is so bright, watch the secret sun fall
There's magic in her hands
Whisper what the future holds